https://www.pezcollectors.com/privacy.html

All Products
Your cart is empty.
Gift CertificatesOn SaleHot ItemsNew PezAll Products
New Pez - [more]
Privacy Notice
We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy lets you know how your personal information is processed and used at PezCollectors.com. We take extraordinary steps to use your personal information only in ways that are compatible with this Privacy Policy. Information CollectionPezCollectors.com is the sole owner of the information collected from our website. We do not, and will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in our privacy statement below. CookiesA cookie is a piece of data stored on the visitors hard drive containing information about the visitor. At this time PezCollectors.com uses cookies only for login convenience. Log FilesPezCollectors.com keeps log files on broad fields to analyze trends, track user movements, and gather data for demographic locations. This is not attached in anyway to visitors personal identification. SharingAt this time, PezCollectors.com does not share any information with advertisers, merchants, or any other third party. LinksLinks to other sites outside of PezCollectors.com do not apply to this privacy statement. We are not responsible for privacy policies of other websites linked to PezCollectors.com. Please read the privacy statement of each website linked to PezCollectors.com for information and data use for visitors personal identification. Our privacy statement applies solely to PezCollectors.com. NewsletterYou can either elect to subscribe or unsubscribe to our newsletter at any time. All information stored on our database is not shared or sold to any third party what so ever. Subscribers wishing to unsubscribe to our newsletter can select the unsubscribe option on our home page at any time. Sending to a FriendWhen a visitor chooses to send product descriptions to a friend, the names and e-mail addresses are not logged. PezCollectors.com will send the friend a one-time e-mail inviting them to visit our site. PezCollectors.com will never send another e-mail to the visitor or friend for any purpose. Changes of our PolicyIf and when our policy statement changes, visitors with Memberships in our databases will be notified of the changes, and provided a link to this page to view the changes. If a visitor decides that our policy does not benefit them, they can use the opt-out option at anytime.
Back
Desktop VersionMonthly Newsletter
Copyright © 2020 Pez Collectors Store, a division of Candy Collectibles, LLC.The Pez Collectors Store and www.pezcollectors.com are not affiliated or endorsed in any way, shape or form with PEZ© Candy, Inc. PEZ© and the PEZ© name are registered trademarks of PEZ© Candy, Inc.
